{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145275672","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145275671"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145277782","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145277782"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145279839","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145279839"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145282971","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145282970"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145285154","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145285154"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145287331","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145287330"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145290132","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145290132"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145292278","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145292278"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145294415","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145294415"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145297572","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145297572"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145299695","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145299694"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145301830","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145301829"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145304834","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145304833"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145307026","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145307026"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145309269","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145309269"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145312351","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145312351"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145314660","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145314659"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145317028","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145317028"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145320078","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145320078"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145322237","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145322236"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145324374","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145324373"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145327554","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145327554"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145329722","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145329722"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145331917","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145331917"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145335127","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145335126"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145337514","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145337514"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145339912","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145339911"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145343065","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145343064"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145345349","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145345348"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145347643","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145347642"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145350653","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145350653"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145352884","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145352883"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145355140","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145355140"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145358104","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145358104"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145360490","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145360489"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145362861","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145362860"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145366001","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145366001"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145368362","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145368361"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145370766","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145370765"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145373752","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145373751"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145376037","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145376036"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145378317","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145378316"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145381617","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145381617"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145383910","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145383910"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145386201","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145386200"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145389613","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145389612"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145392086","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145392085"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145394549","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145394549"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145397463","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145397463"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145399642","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145399641"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145401828","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145401827"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145405256","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145405256"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145407585","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145407584"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145409937","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145409936"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145413089","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145413089"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145415373","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145415373"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145417651","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145417651"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145420692","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145420691"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145422848","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145422848"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145424936","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145424936"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145427996","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145427996"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145430181","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145430181"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145432378","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145432377"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145435529","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145435529"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145437713","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145437713"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145439920","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145439920"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145443173","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145443172"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145445549","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145445548"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145447863","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145447863"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145450997","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145450997"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145453347","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145453346"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145455667","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145455666"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145459079","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145459078"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145459188","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145459187"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" eea4d805-b440-4d82-96e6-c3d0e5a19aab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145521253","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145521253"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" 7fe303ef-4cf6-498d-bc05-9d814a74203c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145523497","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145523497"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" 7fe303ef-4cf6-498d-bc05-9d814a74203c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145525733","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145525732"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" 7fe303ef-4cf6-498d-bc05-9d814a74203c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145569323","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145569323"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" 7fe303ef-4cf6-498d-bc05-9d814a74203c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145577749","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145577748"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" 7fe303ef-4cf6-498d-bc05-9d814a74203c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145577810","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145577810"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" 7fe303ef-4cf6-498d-bc05-9d814a74203c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia zingine ziliona jinsi familia ya milimani ilivyoishi vizuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145589861","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145589860"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" ef784459-cc4f-4582-943a-acf9699041ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SABUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" SABUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145598335","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145598335"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" ef784459-cc4f-4582-943a-acf9699041ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SABUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" SABUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145599940","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145599940"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" ef784459-cc4f-4582-943a-acf9699041ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAHANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" SAHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145604069","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145604069"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" ef784459-cc4f-4582-943a-acf9699041ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAHANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145605640","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145605640"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" ef784459-cc4f-4582-943a-acf9699041ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUFURIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" SUFURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145610916","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145610915"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" ef784459-cc4f-4582-943a-acf9699041ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUFURIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145612525","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145612525"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" ef784459-cc4f-4582-943a-acf9699041ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" SIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145656489","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145656489"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" ef784459-cc4f-4582-943a-acf9699041ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" SIMAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145656628","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145656628"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" ef784459-cc4f-4582-943a-acf9699041ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" SIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145665035","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145665035"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" ef784459-cc4f-4582-943a-acf9699041ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" SIMAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145672118","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145672117"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" ef784459-cc4f-4582-943a-acf9699041ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" SIMAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145693042","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145693042"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" ef784459-cc4f-4582-943a-acf9699041ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" SIMAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145693096","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145693096"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" 73ec0e85-86ae-4d33-8302-0adb533cfcf8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550145706580","data":{"timestamp":" 1550145706579"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_145420"," gameId":" 73ec0e85-86ae-4d33-8302-0adb533cfcf8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitamsomea nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}